Imagine this scene: it's blowing a gale outside, you're snuggled up on the sofa under a warm duvet, chatting and reminiscing with your closest friends.
想象一下这个场景：外面正刮着大风，你在温暖的羽绒被下依偎在沙发上，和你最亲密的朋友们聊天、追忆往事。
That content, snug feeling has a name in Danish - 'hygge'.
那种满足、舒适的感觉在丹麦语中有个名字——“hygge”。
And, as Denmark recently won the title of 'happiest country in the world', the rest of the world is becoming more and more interested in finding ways to embrace this concept.
而且，由于丹麦最近赢得了“世界上最幸福的国家”的称号，世界上其他地方的人们对找到接受这个概念的方式越来越感兴趣。
'Hygge' - originally from a Norwegian word meaning 'wellbeing' - doesn't have an exact equivalent in English.
"hygge" -最初来自一个挪威单词，意思是“幸福”——在英语中没有完全对等的词。
It's often translated as cosiness, or as blogger Anna West told the BBC, "cosiness of the soul."
它常被翻译成“舒适”，或者就像博主安娜·韦斯特告诉英国广播公司的那样，“心灵的舒适”。
But, as translator ToveMaren Stakkestad explains: "Hygge was never meant to be translated.
但是，正如翻译托芙·马伦·斯塔克斯特德解释的那样：“hygge从来就不是用来被翻译的。
It was meant to be felt."
它是用来被感受的。”
Essentially, Hygge involves creating a warm, cosy atmosphere and enjoying it with your loved ones.
从本质上讲，“hygge”包括营造一种温暖、舒适的氛围，并和你所爱的人一起享受它。
Danish winters are long and dark and so achieving 'hygge' is particularly relevant during this season.
丹麦的冬天又长又暗，所以在这个季节实现“hygge”意义非凡。
A typical 'hygge' activity during winter could be, enjoying delicious homemade food and light-hearted conversation with friends - preferably in the warm glow of candlelight; or maybe sipping a glass of mulled wine in the hot tub after a day spent skiing.
冬天典型的“hygge”活动可能是，和朋友们一起享用美味的自制食物，进行轻松愉快的交谈——最好是在温暖的烛光下；或者在滑了一天雪后，在热水浴缸里抿上一杯热葡萄酒。
However, Hygge isn't only confined to the bleak winter months - it can also describe that warm, fuzzy feeling you get after a walk through a forest with friends on summer's day or a family barbecue in the park.
然而，“hygge”并不只局限于萧瑟的冬季月份——它也可以用来形容在夏天和朋友们在森林里散步后，或者在公园里进行家庭烧烤后那种温暖、惬意惬意的感觉。
The concept of 'hygge' is currently taking the world by storm with more and more people becoming obsessed with achieving a state of wellbeing.
"hygge"的概念目前正风靡全球，越来越多的人痴迷于达到一种幸福的状态。
Articles, books and stocking fillers, full of tips on how to achieve hygge, are hitting the market.
充满了如何实现“hygge”的小贴士的文章、书籍和圣诞小礼物正在进入市场。
Although, some believe this has become a marketing and advertising ploy, the benefits of staying happy cannot be underestimated.
尽管有些人认为这已经变成了一种营销和广告策略，但保持快乐的好处不容小觑。
So, as the winter nights draw in, instead of hibernating, get into your favourite onesie, bake some cookies and curl up by a roaring fire with a good book.
所以，随着冬夜的降临，不要冬眠，穿上你最喜欢的连体衣，烤一些饼干，在熊熊燃烧的炉火旁蜷缩着，读一本好书。
And if you can do this with friends and family, even better — hygge is meant to be shared.
如果你能和朋友和家人一起这样做，那就更好了——“hygge”就是要分享的。